# Stefania Gambino UX/UI DESIGNER



#### About me

My name is Stefania, I'm a Digital Designer, specialized in UX/UI Design and Industrial Design with a biomedical focus.
Although my background may seem unconventional for a career in design, it has provided me with a unique perspective on User Experience and a skill set that enables me to communicate effectively with engineers and developers.

My greatest strength is the ability to maintain a **holistic view** of a project, ensuring that all elements are coherent and aligned with the end-user's needs.

#### Contact me

Phone: +39 3282362741

Email: stegambino91@gmail.com

Address: Corso Regina Margherita, Torino

#### Education

Start2Impact University - Master in UX/UI Design 2022-2023

Politecnico di Torino - **Bachelor's Degree in Biomedical Engineering**2011-2019

# Work Experiences

T.rem3die - Biomedical Engineer

Working in a dynamic and constantly evolving environment has enhanced my problem-solving skills. Additionally, I have developed critical and analytical thinking. 2020–2022

#### Freelance Graphic Designer

I have worked on logos, visual communication, and web design for small businesses. I have learned to manage my time and interact with clients. 2017–2020

#### Interests







Science

Travelling

#### Social

LinkedIn: <u>stefania-gambino</u>

Behance: <u>stefaniagambino</u>

# Design Skills







Illustrator

Photoshop

Indesign



HTML



CSS

Figma

## Languages

- Italian Native speaker
- English IELTS (B2)

### **Soft Skills**

Teamworking Problem solving

Accuracy Curiosity

Listening and synthesis skills

Continuous learning

# Visit my portfolio

<u>Portfolio</u>

